<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pautívate</string>
    <string name="toolbar_tittle_main">Pautivate</string>
    <string name="active_breaks">Active Break</string>
    <string name="pausas_in_30">30 min. Breaks</string>
    <string name="pausas_in_60">1 Hour Breaks</string>
    <string name="pausas_in_120">2 Hours Breaks</string>
    <string name="custom_time_work">Set time to begin your active breaks</string>
    <string name="mediaHour">30 minutes</string>
    <string name="twoHour">2 hours</string>
    <string name="oneHour">1 hour</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="custom_time_text">Custom Time</string>
    <string name="custom_time">Duración personalizada para iniciar tus pausas activas - Custom time to begin your active breaks</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="hint_minutes">Minutes</string>
    <string name="timeForActiveBreaks">Time to begin your active breaks</string>
    <string name="eyes">Eyes</string>
    <string name="headNeck">Head and Neck</string>
    <string name="hands">Arms and Hands</string>
    <string name="backTrunk">Torso and Back</string>
    <string name="kneefeet">Knee and Feet</string>
    <string name="seatedAlone">Seated</string>
    <string name="pautivate">Pautivate</string>
    <string name="pautivateX">¡Pautivate!</string>
    <string name="exercises">Excercise</string>
    <string name="exercise1">Excercise 1</string>
    <string name="exercise2">Excercise 2</string>
    <string name="exercise3">Excercise 3</string>
    <string name="exercise4">Excercise 4</string>
    <string name="exercise5">Excercise 5</string>
    <string name="exercise6">Excercise 6</string>
    <string name="exercise7">Excercise 7</string>
    <string name="exercise8">Excercise 8</string>
    <string name="exercise9">Excercise 9</string>
    <string name="exercise10">Excercise 10</string>
    <string name="textExerciseOneEyes">Do circular motions with your eyes without moving your head. Repeat it three time to the right and three times to the left.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseTwoEyes">Look to the right, then straight ahead, look to the left, and straight ahead again without moving your head. Do three reps.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseThreeEyes">Look up and down without moving your head. Do three reps.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseFourEyes">Close your eyes with strength and open them. Do three reps.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseFiveEyes">Coven and uncover your eyes with your hands cupped. Your eyes must be wide open. Do three reps.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseOneHeadNeck">Rotate your head to each side over your shoulder. You must do a pause in the middle. Do three reps.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseTwoHeadNeck">Cross your hands behind your head, flex your neck until the chin touches the chest. Do three reps.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseThreeHeadNeck">Flex your neck to each side, trying to touch each shoulder with your ear. Keep it for a few seconds. Do three reps.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseFourHeadNeck">Rotate your head looking towards a side. Incline the chin until the shoulder, rotating, go down to your chest and look straight ahead.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseOneArmHand">Take, alternately, each arm, flexing it behind the head, and, with the opposite hand apply pressure on each elbow towards the contrary side. Do three reps for each arm</string>
    <string name="textExerciseTwoArmHand">Take the elbows for the front, stretching the arm at chest level and with the other hand apply a slight pressure towards the opposite shoulder. Do three reps for each arm.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseThreeArmHand">Rest the right hand over the left shoulder and, with the opposite hand, apply to a slight pressure over the elbow backwards. Do three reps for each arm.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseFourArmHand">Stretch the arms forwards, then open and close the hands. Do three reps.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseFiveArmHand">Massage the fingers of each hand from the inside to the outside with circular motions and repeat it with the opposite hand.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseSixArmHand">Do a massage around the whole hand and repeat it with the opposite hand.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseSevenArmHand">Stretch the arm, at chest level, frontwards, with the palm of the hand pointing towards the front and the fingers down, with the opposite hand, take the thumb from below applying a slight pressure backwards and do three reps for each hand.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseEightArmHand">Stretch your arm forward at chest height with the palm of your hand facing forward and the fingers upward, with the opposite hand press the palm backward, then rotate your hand to make the fingers point downward and make the same pressure backward. Do three repetitions for each hand.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseOneBackTrunk">Cross your hands behind your back and bring them up keeping your back straight. Perform three repetitions.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseTwoBackTrunk">Put your hands on your shoulders. Rotate the spine to one side until you look back, hold the position for a few seconds, return to the center, make a pause and turn to the other side. Perform three repetitions.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseThreeBackTrunk">With the knees bent and shoulder width apart, lean the trunk sideways with the back straight, place the respective hand on the knee and the opposite hand on the head. Make three repetitions on each side.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseFourBackTrunk">cross one foot over the other with the arms pointing downwards, lean the trunk forward. Hold this position for a few seconds and then repeat crossing the other foot.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseOneKneeFeet">Take the foot with the hand on the same side and stretch the muscle trying to bring the heel closer to the hip. Do three repetitions for each leg.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseTwoKneeFeet">With your feet parallel, take one step forward, bend your forward leg and stretch the other backward, keeping your back straight. Do three repetitions for each leg.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseThreeKneeFeet">Stretch one leg forward and flex the other keeping your back straight. Do three repetitions for each leg.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseFourKneeFeet">Stretch one leg forward and with the tip of your foot draw circles in and out. Make three repetitions with each foot.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseFiveKneeFeet">With your leg extended, move it forward and backward from the hip as if kicking a ball. Do three repetitions for each leg.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseSixKneeFeet">With your leg extended, move it to the side and then to the center like a pendulum. Do three repetitions for each leg.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseOneSeated">Sit with your back straight against the chair back, stretch your hands forward at chest level, interlace your fingers and raise your hands to stretch them over your head. Hold for a few seconds and do three repetitions.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseTwoSeated">Sit with your back straight with your arms hanging down, slowly lower your head and shoulders bending your trunk, continue until the trunk rests on your thighs.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseThreeSeated">Sit with your back straight and raise one leg at a right angle, press down with your hands on your thigh, alternating the two forces. Do three repetitions for each leg.</string>
    <string name="textExerciseFourSeated">Sit with your back straight and cross your right leg over your left, place your right hand over the thigh of your right leg and turn your trunk and head to the left. Do three repetitions for each leg.</string>
    <string name="notif_body">It's time to make your active breaks.</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="home">Start</string>
    <string name="alarm">Alarm</string>
    <string name="timer">Timer</string>
    <string name="config">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="textTimerNotification">Remaining time to start your active breaks </string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="formato_fecha">dd/mm/yyyy</string>
    <string name="formato_hora">hh:mm</string>
    <string name="add_reminder">Add reminder</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="versionApp">Version 1.0.0</string>
    <string name="design">Desing</string>
    <string name="nataliaLizarazo">Natalia "Cosita Rica" N. Lizarazo S.</string>
    <string name="developer">Developer</string>
    <string name="leninGuerrero">Lenin "El Perro" Guerrero Ramírez</string>
    <string name="model">Model</string>
    <string name="danielDuque">Juan Daniel "El Bandido" Duque F.</string>
    <string name="photography">Photography</string>
    <string name="victorCordero">Victor Leonardo Cordero B.</string>
    <string name="year">2019</string>
    <string name="developBy">Developed By</string>
    <string name="pautivateDescription">It is an app designed to encourage active breaks during the development of your work activities, in order to maintain a correct posture for better health.</string>
    <string name="email18code">10010code@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
</resources>
